

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

CONTACT

hope.gratrix@gmail.com 27877 Starfall Way Murrieta, CA 92563 951-834-4294

linkedin.com/in/hope-gratrix hegratrix.github.io

TECHINCAL SKILLS

HTML
CSS
JavaScript
JQuery
Mobile First
Node.js
Express
React
SQL DB
NoSQL DB
Mongo
Bootstrap
Materialize
Foundation

CERTIFICATIONS

CODING BOOTCAMP University of California Irvine, DCE 2018-2019

HOPE GRATRIX

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a wife and a mother of 4 kids. I have spent the last 22 years raising my kids and volunteering my time and talents at my local schools, church and community. This doesn't make for a very traditional resume, but I have a lot of life experience that has expanded my set of skills in many meaningful ways. I have found a passion for coding and I am excited and hungry for the next stage of my life.

WEB DEVELOPMENT PROJECTS

ONE ORGANIZED ELF

This was a group project based on my idea that became a passion. Our app was made to help you organize all your Christmas needs. It is all customizable and editable to suit your needs and intended to use year after year.

It is an express app with a MySQL database. We also HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery, MySQL, Sequelize, React, Express, Moment, and Foundation.

I did the web design and the functionality of the components. I am still working on this app with the hopes of making it accessible this Christmas. I would like to convert it to a react app to be more efficient In load times and to fine tune it's mobile responsiveness.

Repository: https://github.com/hegratrix/OneOrganizedElf Deployed: https://oneorganizedelf.herokuapp.com/

SCHOOL BOARD ELECTION WEBSITE

About a month into coding bootcamp, my friend began her campaign for school board election. I offered to do her website. I am proud of this website because it turned out to be a bigger task than I first realized, but with my limited knowledge at that point, I used many resources to pull it together. I used basic HTML, CSS and JavaScript. She will be running again in two years, and I will revamp this website with more of the knowledge I have now.

Repository: https://github.com/hegratrix/Linda_Lunn

OTHER PROJECTS

https://hegratrix.github.io/portfolio.html



FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPMENT

CONTACT

Hope.gratrix@gmail.com 27877 Starfall Way Murrieta, CA 92563 951-834-4294

linkedin.com/in/hope-gratrix hegratrix.github.io

SKILLS

Strong People Skills

Public Speaking

Organization

Multi-Tasking

Self-Motivated

Quick Learner

EDUCATION

UC IRVINE DCE 2018-2019

BYU IDAHO 2014-2016

BYU PROVO 1996-1998

GROSSMONTY JR COLLEGE 1993-1995

HOPE GRATRIX

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

EDUCATION INTERVENTION Rail Ranch Elementary School, 2017-2018

- Helped children in grades K-5 who were below grade level in both reading and math
- Created lesson plans based on the needs of each child to help reach them individually and instill the love of learning
- Found creative and meaningful ways to inspire the kids

PTA AUDITOR

Murrieta Valley Unified School District, 2015-2017

- Performed bi-annual audits of the District Council PTA
- Trained auditors from individual schools throughout the school district
- Performed PTA treasurer's training for PTA treasurers from throughout Riverside County

PTA TREASURER

Vista Murrieta High School, 2015-2017

- Performed treasurer duties
- Kept all financial records organized and up to date for full financial transparency
- Presented monthly reports to the PTA Board

PTA PRESIDENT

Rail Ranch Elementary School, 2012-2014

- Learned and develop many skills that I've continued to build on over the years since
- Developed interpersonal skills and leadership skills
- Learned to facilitate others in their duties through support and encouragement without judgement or control

FRANCHISE CO-OWNER Orkin Pest Control, 1998-2003

- Owned and operated an Orkin Pest Control franchise with my husband which we sold to Orkin.
- Kept financial records and was responsible for payroll
- Worked in the office as needed including customer service, setting appointments and coordinating with technicians